Guide to the Time Inc. Subject Files 1889-2015 (bulk 1934-1993) MS 3009-RG 1 MS 3009-RG 1
New-York Historical Society
- Series II: 1961 and Later, 1936-2015; 50 Linear feet (50 boxes)
  - Time Canada: 1972 (Offsite-box 490)
  - Time Canada: 1972 [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R5)
  - Time Canada: 1973-1974 (Offsite-box 490)
  - Time Canada: 1973-1974 [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R5)
  - Time Canada (1): 1975 (Offsite-box 490)
  - Time Canada (1): 1975 [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R5)
  - Time Canada: 1973: Time/B (For Business): New demographic edition for business market (Offsite-box 490)
  - Time Canada: 1973: Time/B (For Business): New demographic edition for business market [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R5)
  - Time Canada (2): 1975 (Offsite-box 490)
  - Time Canada (2): 1975 [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R5)
  - Time Canada (3): 1975 (Offsite-box 490)
  - Time Canada (3): 1975 [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R5)
  - Time Canada (4): 1975 (Offsite-box 491, Folder 1-2)
  - Time Canada: 1976 (Offsite-box 491, Folder 3-4)
  - Time Canada: 1976: Last issue of Canadian editorial section (Offsite-box 491, Folder 5)
  - Time Canada: 1977 and Later (Offsite-box 491, Folder 6)
  - Time Canada: 2003: Edit: 60th Anniversary: Includes Great Moments In Time (Offsite-box 491, Folder 7)
  - Time Customer Service, Inc.: 1987: Tampa (Offsite-box 491, Folder 8)
  - Time Custom Publishing (Offsite-box 491, Folder 9)
  - Time Inc. Custom Publishing: 1996- (Offsite-box 491, Folder 10)
  - TDS Ventures, Inc. (Offsite-box 491, Folder 11)
  - Time for Kids: 2000- (Offsite-box 491, Folder 12)
  - Time Inc. Multimedia/New Media: 1993- (Offsite-box 491, Folder 13)
  - Time International: 1961-1964 (Offsite-box 491, Folder 14)
  - Time International: 1965-1970 (Offsite-box 491, Folder 15-16)
  - Time International: 1971-1972 (Offsite-box 491, Folder 17-18)
  - Time International: 1973 (Offsite-box 491)
  - Time International: 1973 [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R5)
  - Time International: 1974- (Offsite-box 491, Folder 21-22)
  - Time-Life Books: 1961 (Offsite-box 491, Folder 23)
  - Time-Life Books: 1962 (Offsite-box 491, Folder 24)
  - Time-Life Books: 1963-1965 (Offsite-box 491, Folder 25-26)
  - Time-Life Books: 1966-1967 (Offsite-box 492)
  - Time-Life Books: 1966-1967 [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R5)
  - Time-Life Books: 1968-1970 (Offsite-box 492, Folder 2-3)
  - Time-Life Books: 1971-1974 (Offsite-box 492, Folder 4)
  - Time-Life Books: 1970-1972: Time-Life Audio (Offsite-box 492, Folder 5)
  - Time-Life Books: 1975-1982 (Offsite-box 492, Folder 6-7)
  - Time-Life Books: International (Offsite-box 492)
  - Time-Life Books: International [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R5)
  - Time-Life Books: International: 1965-1966: Editions: Robert Laffont (Offsite-box 492)
  - Time-Life Books: International: 1965-1966: Editions: Robert Laffont [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R5)
  - Time-Life Books: 1983 & Later (Offsite-box 492, Folder 11)
  - Time-Life Broadcast: CATV: 1965-1970 (Offsite-box 492, Folder 12-13)
  - Time-Life Broadcast: CATV: 1971 (Offsite-box 492)
  - Time-Life Broadcast: CATV: 1971 [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R5)
  - Time-Life Broadcast: Miscellaneous: 1961-1968 (Offsite-box 492-493)
  - Time-Life Broadcast: Miscellaneous: 1969 (Offsite-box 493, Folder 3-4)
  - Time-Life Broadcast: Miscellaneous: 1970-1972 (Offsite-box 493)
  - Time-Life Broadcast: Miscellaneous: 1970-1972 [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R5)
  - Time-Life Broadcast: Programming: 1969 & Before (Offsite-box 493, Folder 7-8)
  - Time-Life Broadcast: International: 1971 & Before (Offsite-box 493, Folder 9)
  - Time-Life Broadcast: International: 1961-1970 (Offsite-box 493)
  - Time-Life Broadcast: International: 1961-1970 [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R5)
  - Time-Life Cable Communications: 1972 & Later (Offsite-box 493)
  - Time-Life Cable Communications: 1972 & Later [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R5)
  - Time-Life (Corporate): 1992- [empty] (Offsite-box 493, Folder 14)
  - Time-Life Films: 1969 (Offsite-box 493)
  - Time-Life Films: 1969 [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R5)
  - Time-Life Films: 1970: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 493, Folder 16)
  - Time-Life Films: 1970: BBC/T-L Film Agreement (Offsite-box R5)
  - Time-Life Films: 1971: BBC (Offsite-box 493, Folder 17)
  - Time-Life Films: 1971: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 493, Folder 18)
  - Time-Life Films: 1972: America Book Deal (Offsite-box 493)
  - Time-Life Films: 1972: America Book Deal [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R5)
  - Time-Life Films: 1972: BBC (Offsite-box 493, Folder 20)
  - Time-Life Films: 1972: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 493, Folder 21)
  - Time-Life Films: 1973: BBC (Offsite-box 493)
  - Time-Life Films: 1973: BBC [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R5)
  - Time-Life Films: 1973: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 493-494)
  - Time-Life Films: 1973: Miscellaneous [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R5)
  - Time-Life Films: 1974: BBC (Offsite-box 494)
  - Time-Life Films: 1974: BBC [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R5)
  - Time-Life Films: 1974: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 493)
  - Time-Life Films: 1974: Miscellaneous [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R5)
  - Time-Life Films: 1975: Miscellaneous: Jan.-June (Offsite-box 494, Folder 4)
  - Time-Life Films: 1975: Miscellaneous: July-Dec. (Offsite-box 494, Folder 5)
  - Time-Life Films: 1975: BBC (Offsite-box 494, Folder 6)
  - Time-Life Films: 1976: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 494)
  - Time-Life Films: 1976: Miscellaneous [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R5)
  - Time-Life Films: 1975-1978: T-L Television Books: Wild, Wild World of Animals (Offsite-box 494, Folder 8)
  - Time-Life Films: 1977: BBC (Offsite-box 494, Folder 9)
  - Time-Life Films: 1975-1979: T-L Television Books: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 494)
  - Time-Life Films: 1975-1979: T-L Television Books: Miscellaneous [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R5)
  - Time-Life Films: 1976: BBC (Offsite-box 494)
  - Time-Life Films: 1976: BBC [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R5)
  - Time-Life Films: 1977: Talent Associates Acquisition (Offsite-box 494)
  - Time-Life Films: 1977: Talent Associates Acquisition [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R5)
  - Time-Life Films: 1977: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 494)
  - Time-Life Films: 1977: Miscellaneous [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R5)
  - Time-Life Films: 1977: Shakespeare Plays: Book Project Attempt (Offsite-box 494, Folder 15)
  - Time-Life Films: 1977: T-L Television Books: Life Goes to War (Offsite-box 494, Folder 16)
  - Time-Life Films: 1978: BBC (Offsite-box 494, Folder 17)
  - Time-Life Films: 1978: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 494)
  - Time-Life Films: 1978: Miscellaneous [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R5)
  - Time-Life Films: 1979: BBC (Offsite-box 494, Folder 20)
  - Time-Life Films: 1979: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 494, Folder 21-22)
  - Time-Life Films: 1979-1980: Time-Life Satellite Network (Offsite-box 494, Folder 23)
  - Time-Life Films: 1980 & Later (Offsite-box 494, Folder 24)
  - Time-Life Films: 1978-1981: Time-Life Video Club (Offsite-box 494)
  - Time-Life Films: 1978-1981: Time-Life Video Club [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R5)
  - Time-Life Home Video (Offsite-box 494, Folder 26)
  - Time Life Inc.: Formerly Time-Life Books Inc.: 1992- (Offsite-box 494, Folder 27)
  - Time-Life Libraries, Inc. (Offsite-box 494, Folder 28)
  - Time-Life Records: 1961-1962 (Offsite-box 495, Folder 1)
  - Time-Life Records: 1961-1962 [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R5)
  - Time-Life Records: 1963-1964 (Offsite-box 495, Folder 2)
  - Time-Life Records: 1963-1964 [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R5)
  - Time-Life Records: 1965 (Offsite-box 495, Folder 3)
  - Time-Life Records: 1965 [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R5)
  - Time-Life Records: 1966 (Offsite-box 495, Folder 4)
  - Time-Life Records: 1967-1969 (Offsite-box 495, Folder 5)
  - Time-Life Records: 1970 & Later (Offsite-box 495, Folder 6)
  - Time-Life Records: International (Offsite-box 495, Folder 7)
  - Time Warner Trade Publishing: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 495, Folder 8)
  - Time-Life Video: 1971-1973: Speed Reading Course with Dick Cavett (Offsite-box 495, Folder 9)
  - Time-Life Video: 1971-1973: Speed Reading Course with Dick Cavett [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R5)
  - Time-Life Video: 1972-1973: T-L Video Center (Offsite-box 495, Folder 10)
  - Time-Life Video: 1970 (Offsite-box 495)
  - Time-Life Video: 1970 [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R5)
  - Time-Life Video: 1971: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 495)
  - Time-Life Video: 1971: Miscellaneous [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R5)
  - Time-Life Video: 1972: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 495)
  - Time-Life Video: 1972: Miscellaneous [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R5)
  - Time-Life Video: 1973-Spring 1991 (Offsite-box 495, Folder 17)
  - Time-Life Video & Television (TLVT): 1991 & Later (Offsite-box 495, Folder 18)
  - Time Warner Books (Offsite-box 495, Folder 19)
  - Time Warner Cable Group: 1989-1991 (Offsite-box 495, Folder 20)
  - Time Warner Cable Group: 1992- (Offsite-box 495, Folder 21)
  - Time Warner Cable Group: New York 1 News: 24 Hour News Channel (Offsite-box 495, Folder 22)
  - Time Warner Entertainment (Offsite-box 495, Folder 23-24)
  - Time Warner Enterprises: Court TV (Offsite-box 495, Folder 25)
  - Time Warner Enterprises: Six Flags Corporation (Offsite-box 495, Folder 26)
  - Time Warner Enterprises: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 495, Folder 27)
  - Time Warner International Inc. (Offsite-box 495, Folder 28)
  - Time Warner Libraries, Inc. (Offsite-box 495, Folder 29)
  - Time Warner Publishing, Inc. (Offsite-box 495, Folder 30)
  - Time Warner Sports (Offsite-box 495, Folder 31)
  - Time Warner Telecommunications Inc (Offsite-box 495, Folder 32)
  - Time Warner Ventures (Offsite-box 496, Folder 1)
  - Time World Newsradio Service (Offsite-box 496, Folder 2)
  - Travel & Entertainment Accounting Department: 1987 (Offsite-box 496, Folder 3)
  - Treasurer's Office: 1965-1970 (Offsite-box 496, Folder 4)
  - Treasurer's Office: 1971-1980 (Offsite-box 496, Folder 5)
  - Treasurer's Office: 1975: Cost Control Committee (Offsite-box 496, Folder 6)
  - Treasurer's Office: 1981 & Later (Offsite-box 496, Folder 7)
  - TV-Cable Week: 1981: Pre-Publication (Offsite-box 496, Folder 8)
  - TV-Cable Week: 1981: Pre-Publication Dummies (Offsite-box 496, Folder 9)
  - TV-Cable Week: 1981: Pre-Publication (Offsite-box 496, Folder 10)
  - TV-Cable Week: 1982: Pre-Publication (Offsite-box 496, Folder 11)
  - TV-Cable Week: Pre-Publication (Offsite-box 496, Folder 12-13)
  - TV-Cable Week: 1982: Pre-Publication: Prospectus (Offsite-box 496, Folder 14)
  - TV-Cable Week: 1982: Pre-Publication: Dummy (Offsite-box 496, Folder 15)
  - TV-Cable Week: 1982: Pre-Publication (Offsite-box 496, Folder 16)
  - TV-Cable Week: 1983: Pre-Publication (Offsite-box 496, Folder 17)
  - TV-Cable Week: 1983: First Issue (Offsite-box 496, Folder 18)
  - TV-Cable Week: 1983: Last Issue (Offsite-box 496, Folder 19)
  - TV-Cable Week: 1983: Pre-Publication (Offsite-box 496, Folder 20)
  - TV-Cable Week: 1983: Publishing (Offsite-box 496, Folder 22)
  - TV-Cable Week: 1984 (Offsite-box 496, Folder 23)
  - TV-Cable Week: 1983: Edit (Offsite-box 496, Folder 24)
  - TV-Cable Week: 1983: Publishing (Offsite-box 496, Folder 25)
  - Treasurer's Office: 1961- (Offsite-box 496, Folder 26-27)
  - Turner Broadcasting System, Inc. (TBS) (Offsite-box 496, Folder 28)
  - Vibe (Offsite-box 496, Folder 29)
  - Video Group: 1970-1975 (Offsite-box 496, Folder 30-31)
  - Video Group: 1976-2003 (Offsite-box 496-497)
  - Video Group: 1976-2003 [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R5)
  - Video Group: 1985- (Offsite-box 497, Folder 2)
  - Video Group: 1977: Strategic Directions Conference: TV & Film Time Inc. (Offsite-box 497, Folder 3)
  - Wallpaper* (Offsite-box 497, Folder 4)
  - Warner Books (Offsite-box 497, Folder 5)
  - Warner Bros.: Consumer Products (Offsite-box 497, Folder 6)
  - Warner Bros.: International Theatres (Offsite-box 497, Folder 7)
  - Warner Bros.: Television/Lorimar (Offsite-box 497, Folder 8)
  - Warner Bros. Television: WB Network: 2000- (Offsite-box 497, Folder 9)
  - Warner Bros.: WEA Inc. (Offsite-box 497, Folder 9)
  - Warner Communications: 1989-1990 (Offsite-box 497, Folder 11)
  - Warner Communications: 1991- (Offsite-box 497, Folder 12-14)
  - Warner Home Video (Offsite-box 497, Folder 15)
  - Warner Music Group: Ice-T Controversy (Offsite-box 497, Folder 16)
  - Whittle Communications: Channel 1 (Offsite-box 497, Folder 17)
  - Warner Music Group: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 497, Folder 18-19)
  - Washington Star (Offsite-box 497)
  - Washington Star [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R5)
  - Whittle Communications: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 497, Folder 22)
  - Working Woman (Offsite-box 497, Folder 23)
  - Working Woman: in Japan (Offsite-box 497, Folder 24)